Wanting to touch the waxing
and waning moon
I reached out
Even if it was a small,
insignificant step
I traveled my universe
Believing I'll get there someday
Once one person stopped,
more and more did.
People are gathering around my voice.
I...
Even if I must walk down
a path never trodden before
I'm actually being a singer.
Even if I'm dreaming too big,
hoping for too much
She's loosened up completely.
This is perfect.
If she can keep
the audience here till the end,
My hand traverses
a 60 centimeter universe
this should be a success,
and her CD should sell.
And gets closer to
the bright side of the moon
Watch me
See?
Wait, that logo...
That was "ask for the moon."
We should get going.
What? Gimme a sec.
I'll take one copy of your CD.
Um, I'd like one as well.
Me, too.
Th-Thank you so much.
Wow, there's so many people.
It's so strange.
The moment I stopped singing
for lots of people,
lots of people came forward
to listen to me.
Now for my third song, "Half & Half."
I was worried at first, but now
I'm glad I put on this show.
Ugh, I hate the sound of drums.
Can you maybe, like, not play?
Don't be ridiculous.
Okay. So, uh, hello.
We're Celestial.
It's nearly the first anniversary
of our debut,
so we're doing a surprise show
in a memorable place.
Not that I wanted to.
Come on! They're doing a homecoming
concert here today?!
Whoa, isn't that Celestial?
Wow, it's really them!
It's Hizu-chan!
They're performing here again?
This is crazy.
Let's go!
Seriously?
It's like the universe is out
to get me or something.
INOHANA RIKKA
Our first song is...
Did it have a title?
It does! You came up with it!
Oh?
Anyway, here we go.
You're popping a throat drop now?
Just let her be.
Here we go with our first song.
One, two...
How does a three-piece band
have such intensity?
Give me the impulse!
I've traveled a long, long time
Through a darkness
that drowned out my voice
Walking on and on,
as if to find the next stretch
That vocalist is insanely good!
Of this lonely, lonely thread
My voice is buried, down and out
So I'll drag it out and shout
You only get one flicker,
shut everything out
You only get one shot,
blaze a trail and hit your mark
You only get one life,
what will you choose?
Make your heart beat
in the moment, let it shine!
Urp. Whoops, I just burped.
I felt I was all alone
O...
Okay, here's my third song,
I failed to even come into my own
"Half and Half."
It all, all comes to end, like it or not
Then take in the now, now
If your voice was shut off
and locked away
Unleash it and shout
You only get one flicker,
gather it all up
You only get one shot,
blaze a trail and rend the sky
Hey, what is this feeling?
We only have one life,
and that's what we'll choose
Acting like I'm clueless
Rikka's doing great.
But deep down, I know
Her voice sounds way better
than it did in the first song.
Because it's obvious
Make your heart beat
in the moment, let it shine!
She's doing nothing wrong!
And yet, this had to happen.
My world's glittering like
a page out of a shoujo manga
Rikka's not to blame here.
It's my fault for picking this spot!
I don't need confidence or reassurance
Hey, become a musician with me.
Aiko was the one
who asked me to join her.
Hey, why'd you ask me
to team up with you?
Because of your voice, duh.
It was love at first listen.
I knew your voice was a real moneymaker.
Money? Seriously?
I had one more reason.
I'm the type to get front-row tickets
for my favorite singer's shows.
Huh?
You know,
standing next to you is like
being in your front row.
I want to hear your voice
from as close as possible.
Huh.
Together, we wrote a song
called "In the Calm of Night,"
and sent the finished version
to a record label.
"IN THE CALM OF NIGHT"
Hey, they sent a message!
They want to meet us in person!
Yay!
Man, those were the days.
Which one of you sang the chorus?
We only need that girl's voice.
Huh?
You can't do this! We worked together—
Rikka.
I'm happy for you.
Do your best for me too, okay?
She must've had so much to say back then.
I'll lock it all up for now and run
She hid them all behind her smile
and supported me,
To where I can hear your voice
and you can hear mine
but I ran away because of one setback.
With each sway of my hair,
I get one step closer
I stayed in my comfort zone,
sang other people's songs
to be fake popular,
I can hear my panting and my heartbeat
and acted like I hadn't
given up on music.
No wonder she got mad at me.
It must be because I ran so hard
What should I say first?
I just decided to stop singing
for the masses, but this still stings.
Something that's like me
to say, from me to you
Oh no. If I keep looking down,
I might actually cry.
I kept thinking all this while...
But I just can't look up...
Hey! What are you doing, Yamabuki-kun?
I told you, if you're having a hard time
and can't keep your head up,
look in my eyes and nowhere else.
I made the right call in bringing these.
You could see me
even with your teary eyes, huh?
And I told you I'd die of cringe...
What's wrong, Rikka?
Do you really want it to end this way?
Weren't you going to sing
for the person dear to you?!
Are you just going to
let your dream die here?!
Did you ask her to come?
No, I...
He was handing out fliers by the station.
INOHANA RIKKA
STREET PERFORMANCE
I didn't expect her to show up now.
I'm glad I handed it to her just in case.
Aiko, I... I'm sorry!
Sing.
I came here to listen to you sing.
You've never been talkative
or had a way with words.
It's easier for me to know
what you want if you just sing.
Okay.
Got it.
This will be my last number.
I wrote this song for my best friend.
This is "trails."
We're walking towards the rainbow,
you said with a smile
With a smile that shined
like a glass marble
So I packed everything I could think of
In this old backpack of mine
We can go wherever we want,
as far as we want
Until our hands touch
the base of the rainbow
Let's go see things never seen before
Until we wave goodbye
at the crossroads someday
under the rainbow someday
What'd you think?
Not good enough.
What?!
Where's the encore?
Encore? But I only wrote four new songs.
I'm getting tired of this,
so can we call it a day?
I mean, I guess?
Hey!
Listen up, you sheeple!
Rikka's gonna sing
"In the Calm of Night"! Listen!
Huh? What are you doing?!
Lay off me. Those guys piss me off.
Why "In the Calm of Night"?
What, did you forget it?
Like I could ever...
Th-They picked a fight with us! So scary!
Do they want a battle?
What, you scared of battling us?
Bring it, you cowards.
Aiko, quit provoking them.
Eek! I-I don't have any money on me!
How dare they mock us.
Let's go, Hizumi!
It's time for a battle of the bands!
Are you ready?
Y-Yamabuki-kun, stop Aiko!
Where are your balls, Celestial?!
Yamabuki-kun?!
You need to show off here
and make yourself memorable!
What? But...
The spectators are all over there.
It don't matter. Listen up.
Here's "In the Calm of Night,"
special arrangement.
Arrangement?
Come on, get to it.
Ugh, you're always so bossy.
Hey, Aiko. I'm sorry for everything.
I'm sorry for everything, too.
Have I gotten any better at singing?
Beats me.
Meanie.
How am I supposed to tell
with just one song?
I'll listen again, but this time...
As the sun sank into the sea
We let out a deep sigh
And the oceans responded to us
With a big white wave
And dragged the wind away with it
After we saw it off
We made a promise for no reason
The calm takes over the night
When the calm takes over the night
We feel like there's nobody else
in the world but us
The sea blends into the sky
When the sea quietly blends into the sky
I know it's just the two of us
But I still whisper to you
Ah, ah, in the calm of night
IN RIKKA'S FRONT ROW
Okay.
Ready? Cheers to a good concert!
Cheers to that!
Way to go-Iko!
Your show was great, Rikka-chan.
We just happened to be there, okay?
By sheer luck.
Yeah, a total coincidence.
Miracles are real, huh?
Right?
Try to be less obvious.
You even managed to sell
more than 20 copies of your CD.
That's a huge success.
My quota was 50 copies, though.
Still, not bad for a first time, I guess.
Yeah. You did good.
You should've invited
Aiko-chan to join us, too.
Look, I tried, okay?
Hell nah! I'm too shy for that!
Meeting new people is too much for me!
She has all that fire
and she's a shy girl?
I'll just have a private party
with her later.
I'm glad you managed to patch things up.
Huh? Oh, yikes!
I left my wallet in the park!
Seriously?
I'll go get it!
What a cliché.
Is it, though?
Want us to go with you?
Oh, nah. It's fine.
Go on, Errand Boy! Get going!
Go with her and do everything
in your power to help!
See you at school the day after tomorrow.
Bucky, you'd better not
do anything weird, okay?
Bye, Rikka!
What do you mean, weird?
Whoa, the whole car to ourselves.
Lucky me, 'cause my legs are beat.
Wow, look.
The sun's setting over the sea.
It's beautiful.
Why don't you take a seat, too?
Yours truly remains unseated wherever
possible for my lower body health.
Huh...
And you had the prime seat
next to me available, too.
Why do you always miss these chances?
It'd be fine if it was
delivered to lost-and-found,
but where would we look
for it if it wasn't?
He's even more worried
about my wallet than me.
That was nerve-racking, but I had fun.
My heart is still racing.
It was a good show.
You did well seeing it through.
Well, I didn't manage to sell 50 CDs,
but I'm still satisfied.
It's so hot.
I managed to write some good songs, too.
I never thought giving up on mass appeal
to sing for the people I want to reach
would be this fun.
I don't think I picked the wrong approach.
Yeah.
Hey...
Did I really not choose wrong?
Of course you didn't.
You need to have fun before anything else.
I did have fun
until the middle.
But when the audience
I'd attracted left me,
I felt bitter, sad, and really miserable.
I can say I only sing for
certain people all I want,
but it still stings when the audience
abandons me like that.
That wasn't your fault!
Celestial just happened
to do a show nearby!
All it means is that they had my number.
Music is about popularity, and
we're fighting over the same fans.
That's what it means to live as a pro.
I thought you'd be up for it.
Maybe I expected too much of you.
Hello?
Yes, hello. I'm almost at the office.
Yeah, it went great.
INOHANA RIKKA
STREET PERFORMANCE
Do you hate rabbits?
Celestial's show went over great.
It's trending on socials, too.
Oh, also, there was a high
schooler performing nearby.
It was kinda interesting.
That's a peace sign, not a rabbit.
INOHANA RIKKA
STREET PERFORMANCE
So, what does this mean?
I'm thinking of reaching out to her.
This is...
A SYMBOL FOR DEFIANCE
I wonder if Rikka-chan found her wallet.
The errand boy will take care of it.
Wow, you actually trust him.
Huh? It's not like that.
But I guess he is handy to have around.
I'm having him do so much for me.
Farewell!
Don't you run away!
Iko-chan's so tough.
What's that mean?
Anyway, I've got stuff to do, too.
Oh, okay.
Bye-bye.
See ya.
I don't want to think I chose wrong.
But maybe everything I've been saying
is just an excuse to run away
from the competition?
Rikka...
Can I really keep
pursuing music like this?
Hey...
Why are you crying?
Forgive me. I deserve the blame.
Huh?
I should've known there was a chance
Celestial would show up there.
If I had researched more thoroughly...
You did nothing wrong!
Your songs, your vocals...
They were all good!
This is all my fault!
Stop that.
I wanted this show to become
a fun memory for you, and yet...
You're blaming yourself too much.
Nobody could've seen that coming.
The next stop is Kaihin-Makuhari.
O-Oh no!
Now arriving at Kaihin-Makuhari.
What's wrong?
I'm a Yamabuki! Nobody can see my tears!
What are you, famous?
You never know who's watching and where!
Once you deface your name,
fixing it is difficult!
Yeesh. What am I to do with you?
The train on platform number one
is a local train for Soga.
Check out the lovebirds.
It's good to be young.
TRANSLATION: SRIRAM GURUNATHAN
TIMING: MARIANA MARTINEZ
EDITING: WILLIAM HAGGARD
You went above and beyond
for me, Yamabuki-kun.
QUALITY CHECK: S BILYEU
TRANSLATION CHECK: MICHELLE TYMON
The rest was up to me.
I'm sorry I suck so bad.
You do not.
Compared to Celestial, I do.
But you showed more heart.
I love your music more.
You sure that's an opinion
my producer should have?
Showing more heart
doesn't mean it'll resonate.
That's just pretty, idealistic nonsense.
Is it?
It is.
ANCHORING 101
VOICE ACTRESS PERSONALITY QUIZ!!
So very pretty.